shortform.com 2012-05-25

# ShortForm

* * *

ShortForm.tv respects your privacy. Although the site does not require personal information to be used, should you provide personal information, for example by creating an account and logging in, that personal information (such as name and contact information) will not be released, sold, or rented to parties outside ShortForm.tv.

ShortForm.tv may accumulate data on the videos users like and dislike, share, or otherwise interact with. One purpose of this information is to improve the quality of material shown to each user. Another purpose is to tailor advertising content to individuals.

In addition to information about viewing preferences, ShortForm.tv makes use of third party services, such as Google Analytics, to measure site traffic.

ShortForm.tv may use cookies. A "cookie" is a small data file that is placed in your browser, allowing ShortForm.tv to recognize return visitors.

While ShortForm.tv will strive to protect personal information, it cannot guarantee the safety of information transmitted through the Internet. Users must always take care entering and maintain personal information, as there are points of risk beyond the control of any single entity.

#### Content Disclosure

ShortForm.tv aggregates video content from a variety of sources. The views and opinions expressed in material appearing on ShortForm.tv are those of the original creators. To the extent that ShortForm.tv produces its own material, where that material is intended to represent the opinion of the company, it will be clearly identified.

ShortForm.tv accepts a variety of advertising, sponsorships, paid insertions, and other forms of commercial content, some of which may not be obviously commercial. Advertising may influence the content shown on ShortForm.tv.
